<archimate:BusinessObject
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Operational Enabler"
    id="id-ac8ed41b-adbb-46e1-a8a5-24ba042266c7"
    documentation="An organisation, person, object or event that makes it possible to formulate or implement the a public policy.&#xA;&#xA;Based on Hill, M. and Hupe, P, Implementing Public Policy: Governance in Theory and in Practice, SAGE  Publications Ltd 2002  &#xA;&#xA;An [Operational Enabler] is influenced by a [Public Policy Implementation Approach] and a [Public Policy Implementation Mandate] which determine the role of the organisation, person, object or event.&#xA;This role is determined by the following quadrant:&#xA;&#xA;                                                                                          | Public Policy Implementation Approach | &#xA;                                                                                          |___________________________________________|&#xA;                                                                                          | Top / Centralised     | Down / Delegated  |&#xA;______________________________________________________|______________________|____________________|&#xA;                              |                                                           |                                    |                                  |&#xA;Public                   | Strongly / Low Level Regulated    |               A                  |               B                 |&#xA;Policy                   | ___________________________________| _____________________| ____________________|&#xA;Implementation |                                                            |                                    |                                  |&#xA;Mandate              | Softly / High Level Regulated        |                C                 |                D               |&#xA;__________________| ___________________________________|______________________|____________________|  &#xA;&#xA;Option A: Public Policy Implementation Mandate: Strongly / Low Level Regulated, Public Policy Implementation Approach: Top / Centralised&#xA;SETTING THE PUBLIC POLICY KEY IMPLEMENTATION IOP INSTRUMENTS (i.e. focus on data architecture like a base registry solution)&#xA;&#xA;Option B: Public Policy Implementation Mandate: Strongly / Low Level Regulated, Public Policy Implementation Approach: Down / Delegated&#xA;SETTING PUBLIC POLICY IMPLEMENTATION STANDARDS AND RULES (i.e. focus on technology architecture like eID tech specifications)&#xA;&#xA;Option C: Public Policy Implementation Mandate: Softly / High Level Regulated, Public Policy Implementation Approach: Top / Centralised&#xA;SETTING PUBLIC POLICY IMPLEMENTATION OBJECTIVES (i.e. focus on business architecture like a  national interoperability strategy)&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Option D: Public Policy Implementation Mandate: Softly / High Level Regulated, Public Policy Implementation Approach: Down / Delegated&#xA;SETTING PUBLIC POLICY IMPLEMENTATION  FRAMEWORKS AND COLLABORATION PROTOCOLS CROSS THE DIFFERENT DELEGATION LEVELS (i.e. focus on application architecture like a national reference architecture)&#xA;&#xA;The following implementation is an example on how this specific Architecture Building Block (ABB) can be instantiated as a Solution Building Block (SBB):&#xA;The Customs 2020 Programme&#xA;Customs 2020 is an EU cooperation programme providing national customs administrations with the possibility to create and exchange information and expertise. It allows developing and operating major trans-European IT systems in partnership and establishing various human networks by bringing together national officials from across Europe. The programme has a budget of € 547.3 million and will run for 7 years from January 1 2014.&#xA;https://ec.europa.eu/taxation_customs/business/customs-cooperation-programmes/customs-2020-programme_en">
  <properties
      key="ID"
      value="ABB166"/>
  <properties
      key="dct:type"
      value="eira:OperationalEnabler"/>
  <properties
      key="dct:publisher"/>
  <properties
      key="dct:modified"/>
  <properties
      key="eira:ABB_Status"
      value="Obsolete"/>
</archimate:BusinessObject>
